therabreath.com 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy | TheraBreath

Here at TheraBreath, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

##### 

  1. What information do we collect and how do we use it?
  2. How does Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath protect customer information?
  3. What are cookies and what do they do?
  4. Will Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
  5. How does Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath allow customers be removed from promotional emails?
  6. How does Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath protect the privacy of the children younger than 13?
  7. Your consent

#### What information do we collect and how do we use it?

When you order, we need to know your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.

When you sign up for services like the Questionnaires or download certain software such as the eBooks, we may ask for demographical information. We use the information to better understand our customers.

We may personalize your shopping experience by using your purchase and site behavior to shape our recommendations about our other products and merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic and patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the site

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath products, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, visit http://www.therabreath.com/emailoptions.asp and enter your email address. If you have more than one email address, please include the others in your email. Please note that you will be removed from our email distribution list and will no longer receive any promotional emails from us. If you place an order with us, you will still receive emails pertaining to any purchases you make from us.

We will never share your personal information with any third-party. On rare occasions we may notify you (with your permission) about a new product or service from a third-party that we endorse. However this contact will always initiate from us and your information will never be passed to that third party.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for our Service. Non-personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely.

**For visitors outside the USA and Canada:** Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath does not knowingly market to or solicit users from countries other than the United States and Canada. We do not knowingly collect or store data from users outside of the United States or Canada. We do not ship to International addresses or accept International billing addresses. If you are residing in other countries, you are discouraged from submitting data of any kind, including email addresses and if you do so, you agree that TheraBreath.com and Dr. Harold Katz, LLC are not liable for your data collection or storage. To access TheraBreath products and services from countries other than the United States or Canada, please click here.

#### How does Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath protect customer information?

Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath uses the latest encryption technology to keep your personal information safe. All of your ordering information -- including your name, address, and credit card number — is encrypted using a secure server for maximum security. Your credit card and billing information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system. We're so certain that our online order systems are secure that we back it up with a guarantee. In the unlikely event that you are subject to fraudulent charges, remember to first notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. If, for whatever reason, you are held responsible for any fraudulent charges made on our site, Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath will cover the entire liability for you, up to $50, as long as the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made from Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath while using our secure server.

Credit card transactions are handled by a third-party financial institution, which receives the credit card number and other personal identifying information only to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions. If you feel more comfortable doing so, you are welcome to call in your credit card information and complete your purchase by phone. Please call 1 (800) 973-7374 between the hours of 8:00 - 5:00 PST Monday - Friday.

#### What are cookies and what do they do?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our site uses cookies to speed navigation, keep track of items, and provide you with custom-tailored content. We use cookies to remember information you gave to us so you don't have to reenter it each time you visit our site. By showing us how and when shoppers use our site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not.

Many improvements and updates to our site are based on the data derived from these cookies, such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of ads served. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies however you will not be able to take advantage of all the features and pages with Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath's website.

#### Will Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

We will never share your personal information with any third-party. On rare occasions we may notify you (with your permission) about a new product or service from a third-party that we endorse. However this contact will always initiate from us and your information will never be passed to that third party.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for our Service. Non-personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely.

#### How does Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath allow customers be removed from promotional emails?

To unsubscribe from our emails, simply visit http://www.therabreath.com/emailoptions.asp and enter your email address. If you have more than one email address, please include the others in your email. Please note that you will be removed from our email distribution list and will no longer receive any promotional emails from us. If you place an order with us, you will still receive emails pertaining to any purchases you make from us.   

#### How does Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath protect the privacy of the children younger than 13? 

Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath is concerned about the privacy of young children and does not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We suggest that you become involved with your child's access to the Internet and to our site to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected. 

#### Your consent

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Dr. Harold Katz, LLC/ TheraBreath. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

_This privacy policy was last modified on May 25, 2018._
